<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VulCANWash</string>

    <string name="booking_title">Booking Confirmation</string>
    <string name="booking_message">Would you like to book at %1$s?</string> <!-- %1$s will be replaced by shop name -->
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>


    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        <![CDATA[
            Effective Date: December 1, 2024 \n\n

            Welcome to VulcanWash! By using this app, you agree to the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully before proceeding. \n\n

            1. General Use \n
            1.1. By accessing and using VulcanWash, you agree to be bound by these terms. \n
            1.2. You must be at least 18 years old or have parental/guardian consent to use this app. \n\n

            2. User Account \n
            2.1. Users are required to provide accurate and complete information during account creation. \n
            2.2. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your login credentials. \n
            2.3. VulcanWash is not liable for any unauthorized access to your account. \n\n

            3. Services Provided \n
            3.1. VulcanWash connects users with vulcanizing services and their auto needs. \n
            3.2. Service availability and pricing are subject to change without notice. \n
            3.3. VulcanWash does not guarantee the availability of any specific service provider. \n\n

            4. Payments \n
            4.1. All payments for services booked through the app must be made as per the specified terms. \n
            4.2. Refunds and cancellations are subject to the policies of the respective service provider. \n\n

            5. User Conduct \n
            5.1. Users must not use VulcanWash for any unlawful or prohibited activity. \n
            5.2. Harassment, abuse, or inappropriate behavior towards other users or service providers is strictly prohibited. \n
            5.3. VulcanWash reserves the right to suspend or terminate accounts violating these rules. \n\n

            6. Liability \n
            6.1. VulcanWash acts as an intermediary and is not responsible for the quality or delivery of services provided by third parties. \n
            6.2. VulcanWash is not liable for damages resulting from misuse of the app or errors in service delivery. \n\n

            7. Privacy \n
            7.1. Your personal information is collected and used in accordance with our Privacy Policy. \n
            7.2. By using VulcanWash, you consent to the collection, use, and sharing of your information as outlined in the Privacy Policy. \n\n

            8. Changes to Terms \n
            8.1. VulcanWash reserves the right to modify these terms at any time. \n
            8.2. Users will be notified of significant changes, and continued use of the app constitutes acceptance of the revised terms. \n\n

            9. Contact Us \n
            For any questions or concerns about these terms, please contact us at: \n
            Email: vcwash.app@gmail.com

        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>